<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call me how</title>
    <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Call me how</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 11:56:54 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://howchanghong.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Impermanence</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/impermanence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 11:56:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/impermanence/</guid>
      <description> The ephemeral nature of things should not evoke despair but gratitude for the present moment and a serene sadness at the beauty and fragility of the world.
 &amp;ldquo;Cherry blossoms in the evening. Ah well, today also belongs to the past.&amp;rdquo; Issa
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Skills</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/study-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 21:24:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/study-skills/</guid>
      <description>Study Skills How to Study more Effectively and Efficiently
PURPOSE While Singapore’s education is very holistic in terms of the subjects that is taught, the education system fails to teach students how to be a better learner and study better. This guide is not a holy grail, but an individual’s experience and culmination of knowledge and strategies developed through my years of study.
Overview  Learning Science Time Management Notes Making Classroom lessons Exam Mugging Sessions Exam Strategies  1) Learning Science 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description> https://howchanghong.github.io/webVR/  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Drives Behaviour</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/system-drives-behaviour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/system-drives-behaviour/</guid>
      <description>Instead of throwing out empty motivational speeches or trying to depend on a few superstars to carry the organisation, it is the job of the leader to architect a system that helps to drive a enterprising culture and mold the behaviours of its people. When the system&amp;rsquo;s conditions, connections and culture is right, each individual will be able to assemble themselves and align their senses of worth to the organisation&amp;rsquo;s direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Truth</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/temporal-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/temporal-truth/</guid>
      <description>Our notion of truth is based on the information and knowledge we possess at this point of time. We formulate our world and logic surrounding this state of time and call this information &amp;ndash; truth. However, as our world changes, the information and knowledge can change overtime which alters the truth.
Truth is temporal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emptiness is not Nothingness</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/emptiness-is-not-nothingness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/emptiness-is-not-nothingness/</guid>
      <description>  “No, emptiness is not nothingness. Emptiness is a type of existence. You must use this existential emptiness to fill yourself.” Liu Cixin, The Three-Body Problem
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog in 2019</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/new-blog/</guid>
      <description> Motivation for Blog  Start a new project in 2019 Learn how to setup a static website (using Hugo and Github) Platform to consolidate my thoughts  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 20:31:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>“He who has a why to live for can bear with almost any how,” -Nietzsche
 To live is to learn. I like to fiddle around with little projects on development and design.
Principles Radical Truth, Radical Open-mindedness
Philosophy Nhilism, Utilitarian, Stoicism
Books Genre Psychology and Philosphy
Podcasts The Truth, Pod Save The World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Learnings in 2017</title>
      <link>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/50-learnings-in-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howchanghong.github.io/posts/50-learnings-in-2017/</guid>
      <description>Work has been life these days and the bustling pace can be overwhelming without giving myself a time to reflect. Seeing my brother’s note to do this particular challenge, I’m inspired to do personal reflections myself too. In addition, after making a bet with Yunhan, I shall attempt to make a new experience every week. Thus, the objectives of this challenge are: Reflect on events that happened this week and, How I felt, what influenced my decisions and what can be done better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>